thank you what a day I had today today I
spent the day converting my son's
bedroom into my
office that should get him to move
out I've tried
everything well it's so nice to be in
front of people you know
yes oh I've been a little depressed you
know we didn't see my wife's family for
Easter we didn't see them for Christmas
and I've been a little depressed cuz I
know at some point we're going to have
to see them
again can't go on
forever so I'm from Boston originally
but I live in Los Angeles now and things
shut down there around March of
2020 so I haven't been to the gym since
1989 I'm going to get back out
there La is a strange place when the
pandemic started I drove by the park in
my neighborhood and I spotted a guy
sunbathing
naked I yelled hey buddy put a mask
[Laughter]
on I saw a doctor on TV one day saying
that we may have to wear masks for the
rest of our lives and I thought I wish
he had told me that before I got my kids
[Applause]
braces I think people are sick of The
Masks I saw someone today getting
harassed for wearing a
mask I was at the bank the poor guy's
just trying to rob the
place
my daughter graduated from college
during the pandemic and her graduation
took place
online and she was so bummed out about
it here's the thing she went to an
online
university I don't know what she's
expecting to be
honest I got in some bad habits during
the pandemic I would stay up late at
night and buy things I shouldn't on
Amazon one night late at night I bought
my hamster a
pelaton that wheel is not enough of a
challenge I had a weird thing happened a
couple weeks ago I looked out on my
front porch and I spotted a
coyote and it was kind of my fault
because I'd ordered a package from
[Laughter]
Acme you have to be a certain age to get
that
[Applause]
joke not as many Road Runner fans as I
had
hoped now one Saturday during the
pandemic it was a little girl next
door's birthday and she couldn't have a
birthday party so all of her friends
drove by her house and beeped and waved
and wished her a happy birthday and it
brought a tear to my eye because that's
how my parents used to celebrate my
birthday so glad the tradition
[Music]
continues I got my will taken care of
during the pandemic my attorney said to
me said when you die do you want to be
buried or cremated so I said surprise
[Laughter]
me no
spoilers I was doing some research on
the internet the other night I
discovered that there had once Been a
Murder in the house that we're currently
living
in it happened 2 years after we moved
in raised a lot of questions
actually I was a little kid my
grandfather died I remember I asked my
mother I said when I die will I see gry
again and she said not if you're
good
[Laughter]
so I've been busy had a job interview
last week the guy asked me like a
hundred questions at one point he said
to me do you
gossip so I said
no but you know who
does I haven't heard back from him
yet little things bother me yesterday
the guy that was supposed to fix our
doorbell did didn't show
up or did
he some Mysteries will never be
solved my aunt retired this week she
worked at the DMV for 40
years 40 years at the DMV and in that
time she waited on nearly a dozen
customers
that I was talking to my neighbors my
neighbor said to me you don't know this
about me but I've had a lot of
Botox only one of us was able to keep a
straight
face my wife did that
ancestry.com she discovered that one of
her ancestors graduated in the first
graduating class at Harvard in
1636 and get this 2 weeks ago he
finished paying off his student
loans I got stopped by the cops last
week the cops said to me you were going
70 in a
50 I said 70 is the new
50 I saw someone hitchhiking the other
day hitchhiking it's so dangerous I came
this close to pulling over and murdering
him
myself just to teach him a
[Laughter]
lesson so had one of those impossible
Burgers you know what I'm talking about
those vegan
hamburgers they're
delicious I had mine with
bacon that's the way to do
it do you have a friend you've known a
long time tell you something that just
blows your mind today my best friend who
have known my whole life revealed to me
that he's
imaginary I didn't see that
coming I was talking to my other friends
he said to me if you had a time machine
would you go back in time and kill Baby
Hitler here's the thing I'm a dad I
don't think I could kill a baby but I
could strangle teenage
[Applause]
Hitler imagine what a nightmare he must
have
been my teenage daughter thinks she
knows everything we're started to
regret naming her
[Laughter]
Alexa my wife told me today that my
daughter's been
shoplifting so now I have to deal with
that I'm going to wait until after my
[Music]
birthday
teenagers the worst the other day my
little girl talked back to my wife my
wife told her to do something she said
no I don't want to I had to pull her
aside and say listen you got to teach me
how to do
that you might be a
genius so I'm from Boston the other day
someone said to me where you from and I
said Boston and he said the
city I said no the '70s rock
band it's More Than A
[Laughter]
Feeling but I I so missed way things
were before the pandemic right when
things were normal I was back in Boston
a couple years ago I visited my
childhood home and I knocked on the door
and I said excuse me I used to live here
can I look
around and
reluctantly my parents let me
[Music]
in what's their
problem I was back in New England about
5 years ago I went to one of those corn
mazes one of those giant corn mazes
I couldn't find my way out I'm wandering
around for like 2 hours
finally I took off all my
clothes because if you're naked Security
will
come security came they got
lost
they took off all their
clothes we were there for
days so I live in LA now it's I like La
it's a strange place on Halloween I
frightened all my neighbors I dressed up
as
[Laughter]
gluten
my neighbor told me that meditating for
40 minutes Every Morning has changed his
life he's late for work he lost his
job his wife left him huge
changes last week my wife put together
an earthquake plan and then in the event
of an earthquake she and the kids are
supposed to stand under the doorway and
I'm supposed to stand under the
chandelier
she went out and bought a
[Music]
chandelier so my wife and I we recently
celebrated our 29th wedding
anniversary oh thanks thanks very much
thank you and I'm happily married I know
that I'm lucky because 50% of married
people say they're unhappily married now
this is going to a poll I took earlier
today at my
house what's her
problem my wife just saying every time
we watch a movie together she falls
asleep in the first five
minutes every time she doesn't even know
I'm here
tonight
she thinks the two of us are watching
The shash Shack
Redemption my wife's an amazing woman
she knows a lot about wine like she
knows which wine goes with which
breakfast
cereal very
impressive I call my wife
pumpkin cuz she always gets smashed
around around the
holidays
my wife's about a foot shorter than I am
so she has no idea that I'm
[Music]
bald wa till she finds
out my wife has this guy that she's
worked with for years that she refers to
as her work
husband they have three kids
together
it's going very
well I met my wife on jury
duty thanks to me she was
[Applause]
acquitted oh you can't trust DNA
evidence my wife's always shocked when I
actually know something like the other
night we're watching Jeopardy the
question is what's the tallest building
in the world and I said oh that's Burge
Khalifa in Dubai she's like how do you
know that he said well when you parents
are living with us I Googled what should
I jump off
of and that's what came
up my wife is a Psychology major in
college so she's constantly
psychoanalyzing me when I wanted to fire
the pool boy she said you feel
threatened by young veral males because
you're getting older and you're coping
with your own
mortality and my argument was we don't
have a
pool what is Enrique doing
here
so we start seeing a marriage counselor
and the woman's giving us some very
valuable tips for instance she said when
you first wake up in the morning the
first thing you should say to each other
is I love
you and not you
again good to know good to
know I'm kidding of course my wife is
the best thing happened to me and I say
that because when I met my wife I only
had like 2 minutes of
material she's really come through for
[Music]
me so we've got two kids we're very
fortunate years ago my wife and I we
were told that we were unable to have
children uh by our
landlord
he was completely
mistaken you have to be ready for
anything when you have kids one time my
son was four years old we came back from
the drugstore at the mall he pulls a
candy bar of his pocket now I didn't buy
him a candy bar I knew he didn't pay for
it so we jump back in the car we drive
back to the mall and this time we went
to a jewelry
store
you got a strike why the irons huh
that's what I
[Laughter]
say but people are so full of years ago
our local why had these mommy and me
exercise classes so I called up and said
well can it also be Daddy in me and the
woman in the phone assured me oh
absolutely no problem but then when I
show up with my
dad
[Laughter]
so different being a parent these days
every kid is on medication these days
both my kids are on
Rogan they
insisted my wife was the one that talk
to me into shaving my head she said I'll
look much younger and I do I now look
like I'm a week
old wasn't really what I was going
for so my kids are getting older I've
got two teenagers I've got two kids in
college and it was very hard for me when
my kids went away to college but they
both English Majors so we know they'll
be back living with us in a couple of
years silver
lining my son always calls me when he's
drunk and I'm flattered that he calls me
you know because he's just got the one
phone
[Laughter]
call this year my daughter is taking a
couple classes in philosophy where they
ask the big questions like what is truth
and
what is the meaning of life I like to
ask the little questions like why am I
paying for
this so my son graduates next year and
for his graduation present we're
thinking of getting him a car because
we're pretty sure he's going to become
an Uber
[Laughter]
driver you want to prepare them for
their future so of course now that I'm a
dad I'll call my dad ask for advice he
always says the same thing how' you get
this
number so not
helpful we call our dad gi. Joe my
siblings and I we call him gii Joe
because his name is Joe and he has
gastrointestinal very strange me my
father my father's allergic to Cotton
he's allergic to Cotton he has pills he
can take but he can't get them out of
the
[Laughter]
bottle I do so many stupid things I made
the mistake a few months ago of calling
in sick from the airport do you ever do
this I was about to say why I couldn't
come in you could hear flight 709 is now
boarding flight 7 9 to Vegas is now
boarding so I said I can't come in I'm
hearing
[Laughter]
voices Oh I have a lot of problems I
have that problem with sometimes in the
middle of the night I'll stop breathing
and it's not sleep apnea it's the other
one where your wife's holding a pillow
over your
face I got something in the mail today I
said this is not a Bill opened up said
that was the envelope this is the
bill I bought a box of animal crackers
it said do not eat if seal is
[Laughter]
broken I open it
up sure
enough
the giraffe was
fine all right now who didn't get
that what I don't get these people
instead of buying like a four pack or an
eight pack of toilet paper they buy the
single individual
roll are you trying to
quit
so
stupid so my grandfather came to this
country from Ireland in search of a
better life and then my grandmother
tracked him down and put a stop to
that can nip that in the
butt we always call my grandfather poppy
uh because of his
opium
but it does I've done some research it
turns out I'm super Irish even my blood
type is oh
apostrophe but it's amazing what our
ancestors went through to come to this
country one of my grandfathers came here
in the hull of a ship shoveling coal 14
hours a day all while suffering from
typhoid
fever my other grandfather had even
worse he came to this country on Spirit
[Laughter]
Airlines can you
imagine some characters in my wife's
tell me she has an uncle that can tell
you exactly when and how you're going to
die he's a
hitman
seems like cheating if you ask me when I
was growing up the guy across the street
from us was actually in the mafia and he
was a very nice guy he used to pay me 10
bucks every morning just to start his
car what a
guy
I grew up in a very religious family but
my best friend now is
atheist he said to me how can you
believe God exists when you've never
seen him I said
well I believe Home Depot employees
[Applause]
exist I'm pretty sure they're out
there
when I was growing up we had this little
yellow cat called butter and years later
eventually after we passed away we got a
new little yellow cat called I Can't
Believe It's Not
Butter you guys have had so much fun
thank you so much I appreciate
[Applause]
it
that